<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Info>
    <DefaultInclude>false</DefaultInclude>
    <Description>FAR CRY 4 OPEN WORLD [color=lightblue][b]This mod opens the game up from the start so that you can enjoy it any way you like (even bypassing the campaign if you wish).[/b][/color]



    [list][*]Unlocks all the weapons and signature weapons in the shop (you still have to buy them of course).
    [/list]
    [list][*]Adds the ability to buy attachments for all weapons (aka the Attachments Mod).
    [/list]
    [list][*]Adds back the ACE signature version of the A52 Assualt Rifle that was cut from the game by Ubi (for some starnge reason). You can purchase this just like any other signature weapon.
    [/list]
    [list][*]Removes all the requirements from skills so you can purchase them whenever you like (you still need to acquire them in order - i.e. one health slot, then 2 health slots, then 3 health slots, etc.) but you no longer have to wait until later in the game to buy them nor do you have to do "x" amount of certain things to unlock them.
    [/list]
    [list][*]Opens the North from the very beginning of the game. It will still be covered in fog until you climb bell towers to remove the "fog of war". The Kings Bridge will still warn you "Dangerous Territory Ahead" when you try to go into the north, but the game will not prevent you from doing so should you wish to.
    [/list]
     
    [color=yellow]The only items still "locked" are the items you gain access to from the Trade Agreement Skill (sticky explosives and fire/explosive arrows) since that is the only purpose of the skill. Also the Guns for Hire abilities require certain levels of Karma which makes sense because the Golden Path is only going to help you if you help the people of Kyrat. Otherwise all guns, etc. are unlocked from the very beginning.[/color]

    [size=1][color=lightgreen]Author: [/color][url=https://www.nexusmods.com/users/1251163][b]jvarnes[/b][/url][/size]
    [size=1][color=lightgreen]Ported to the MI format by: [/color][url=https://www.nexusmods.com/users/71678078][b]Amichai-Oz Yannai[/b][/url][/size]
    
    </Description>
    <Category>3</Category>
    <HeaderPicture1></HeaderPicture1>
</Info>
